soufeel.com 2017-06-06

# Terms & Privacy

## PRIVACY AND SECURITY PRIVACY POLICY

Soufeel.com is aware that the security of your private information from the use of our website is an important concern. We take the protection of your personal data very seriously. These terms and conditions cover how we use your personal information. Soufeel continually updates these terms and conditions and we therefore advise you to read them regularly.

## PERSONAL DATA

“When you become a member of Soufeel, we ask you for some personal information, including your name, address, date of birth and email address.”.

Soufeel.com uses this information to fulfill our commitments and provide you with the benefits and services that Soufeel membership entitles you to. When you enter your personal information and submit it to us, you consent to granting Soufeel use this information for the stated purpose.

You are entitled to request this information from Soufeel.com at any time, and we will delete it at your request.

## PURPOSES OF USE

The data we collect will only be used for the purpose of supplying you with the requested products or services or for other purposes for which you have given your consent, except where otherwise provided by law.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
To process transactions, your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.  
To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

## DISCLOSURE

Soufeel.com only uses your personal information for Soufeel administration purposes, and to perform general market analyses, such as purchasing behavior. Soufeel will not disclose your personal information, including your email address, to any third party. And Soufeel does not give other companies access to your registered information.

## CHOICE AND OPT-OUT

If you no longer wish to receive any promotional email from Soufeel.com, you may either click the "UNSUBSCRIBE" button in the email, or contact our customer service.

Name: Advancer Limited  
Address: Third Floor207 Regent Street, London, W1B 3HH, UK 

## QUALITY & WARRANTY

  * 100% Sterling Silver
  * Gems & Stones From Italy
  * Craftsmanship Of 30 Years
  * Jewellery Certificate issued by International Gemological Institute

## PAYMENT & ORDER

Currently, for safety and convenience, we prefer to accept credit card & Paypal as our main payment method.

GB Pounds, U.S Dollars, Australia Dollars,Canadian Dollars and Euro are allowed. Revise & Order Cancel: Within 8 hours upon placing order

To revise or cancel your order, please contacts us within 8 hours after placing order.

Notes: We are not always able to revise or cancel an order already dispatched. Orders has been dispatched will be treated in accordance with our Return policy

Orders will be shipped within 48 hours upon receiving. A tracking number will be e-mailed to you only after 3-4 days from departure. Or check from order status page. For most part of worldwide, the orders are supposed to reach your door. Please track the status of the parcel via the tracking number provided in email. Then, contact local post office for parcel if not received within expected shipping time. Finally, contact us for further information.

Notes: Shipping estimates are from day of shipping not from day of ordering Customers are responsible for lost due to wrong shipping information.

## Cleaning & Maintenance

For cleaning, simply use lukewarm soapy water - that is the best. Use a soft toothbrush to scrub the jewelry and then rinse it in clean water. To remove caked-on dirt, let it soak for 10 minutes in lukewarm soapy water, gently brush it clean and then rinse it in clean water.For a shinier surface, polish your jewelry with a cloth with cleaning solution.

Notes: DO NOT EXPOSE JEWELRY TO CHEMICALS! Silver pieces are given detail by oxidation. Exposure to harsh chemicals can alter the appearance of your SOUFEEL product. These chemicals include, but are not com to, Liquid Silver Polish, Pools, Hot Tubs, and Spas. Oxidized silver and pearls are easily damaged.

## Modifications

Soufeel.com reserves the right to modify this Web Site, and the rules and regulations governing its use, at any time. Modifications will be posted on the Web Site, and users are deemed to be apprised of and bound by any changes to the Web Site. Soufeel.com may make changes in the products and/or services described in this Web Site at any time.

## Disclaimers

If the silver products are damaged or corroded caused by collisions or friction with hard objects, wearing the silver jewelry when bathing or hot springs etc, we are not responsible for any losses. And the behaviors mentioned above will not be protected by our 90 days return policy.

If parcels get lost due to the wrong shipping address provided by customers, we will not burden any losses. Under this condition, a refund will not be available.

## Thanks a lot for your support and attention.

Soufeel.com

Under this agreement, the payment processing services for goods and/or services purchased on this website are provided by www.soufeel.com, having its registered office at Third Floor207 Regent Street, London, W1B 3HH, UK

Name: Advancer Limited
